i know that it's not cool to support israel correct everybody says the middle east conflict
is complicated and they're torn but you need to know that there is nothing complicated about the
situation right now yep nothing complicated about it at all go on the truth is that with hamas
which is an internationally recognized terrorist organization fuck's sake okay let's go back to
the start of your video where you were so close to getting it it's not cool to support israel
why is it not cool to support israel i don't know maybe because it's not cool to support genocide
it's not cool to support ethnic cleansing it's not cool to support apartheid i thought south africa
had taught us that but apparently not it's not cool to support illegal military occupation and
land theft it's not cool to support bombing schools bombing refugee camps bombing fucking hospitals
that is not cool all of you zinists who act as if peace between israel and palestine would be
achievable if it weren't for hamas i swear have fucking rocks in your heads ask yourselves why
the fuck does hamas even exist because this conflict so called has been existing since 1948 and actually
before then and hamas only came into existence in 1987 so